Guide to the Manbites Dog Theater Records, 1987-2017 and undated RL.11437
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Manbites Dog Theater records
1987-2017 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Manbites Dog Theater
RL.11437
28.1 Linear Feet
Manbites Dog Theater was a professional non-profit theater company founded in Durham in October 1987. Manbites Dog staged a variety of theatrical productions, with a focus on premieres of new works by working closely with playwrights, directors, actors, and artists. The theater mounted over 130 productions, many of them regional or state premieres. The theater closed in 2018. Collection includes a variety of administrative documents from these productions, including marketing materials, reviews, contracts, and box-office records. Also includes administrative documents from more general theater operations.
Biographical / Historical
Manbites Dog Theater was a professional non-profit theater company founded in Durham in October 1987. Manbites Dog staged a variety of theatrical productions, with a focus on premieres of new works by working closely with playwrights, directors, actors, and artists. The theater mounted over 130 productions, many of them regional or state premieres. In March 1997, Manbites Dog purchased a building near downtown Durham to serve as a permanent performance space for the company. The building opened to the public in fall 1998. Original production included Indecent Materials, Hotline, Walking Miracles, A Tune for Tommy, Plays Well With Others, Bucknaked: A Love Story, Caleb Calypso and the Midnight Marauders, and Now You See Me. The theater closed in 2018.
Provenance
The Manbites Dog Theater Records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2017, 2018, and 2019.
Collection Overview
Collection includes a variety of administrative documents from the company's productions. Theater Seasons consists of marketing materials, reviews, contracts, and box-office records from individual productions. Some productions include photographs, scripts, and DVD and VHS recordings. Arranged chronologically by season and chronologically by production within each season. Administrative Files comprises materials more broadly related to running the theater company, including receipts, contracts, fundraising materials, and financial records. Includes a few videocassettes. Arranged alphabetically by folder title.
Conditions Governing Access
Original audiovisual materials are closed to patron use. Technical Services staff need to produce use copies before contents can be accessed. Contact the Research Services Department before coming to use this collection.
Community theater -- North Carolina -- Durham; Theater -- North Carolina -- Durham; Theater -- Production and direction; Theater -- Marketing; Durham (N.C.) -- Performance; Manbites Dog Theater
- Theater Seasons, 1987-2017 and undated; 1
  Scope and Contents
  Consists of marketing materials, reviews, contracts, and box-office records related to individual productions. Marketing materials include programs, posters, flyers, postcards, and other handouts. Reviews are primarily newspaper clippings from local and regional papers such as the Raleigh News & Observer, the Durham Herald Sun, and The Independent Weekly. Contracts are between the company and a variety of performers, directors, playwrights, and artists. Box-office records are for individual performances, noting both attendance and revenue. Some productions also include correspondence, expense reports and other financial documents, scripts, photographs, and DVD or VHS recordings. Arranged chronologically by season and chronologically by production within each season.
  Conditions Governing Access
  RESTRICTED: Original audiovisual materials are closed to use. Use of these materials may require production of listening or viewing copies. Please contact Research Services before coming to use this collection.
  - 1987-1988 Season, 1
    - Full season publicity materials, newspaper clippings, flyers, script, 1987-1988 (Box 1)
    - Seventy Scenes of Halloween, 1987 (Box 1)
      Marketing materials
    - Seventy Scenes of Halloween, Twilight Zone, Wheel, Jeopardy, Nature etc. VHS, undated (Box 17, Video-cassette RL11437-VHS-0020)
    - The Polar Express audiocassette, 1988 (Box 17, Audio-cassette RL11437-CS-0002)
    - The Woolgatherer, 1988; 2 folders (Box 1)
      Marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clippings
    - The Woolgatherer, 1988 (Box 16)
      Negatives
    - The Normal Heart, 1988 (Box 1)
    - The Normal Heart, 1988 (Box 16)
      Prograam
    - Twilight Zone: The Elevator; Seventy Scenes of Halloween test tape VHS, 1987 (Box 17, Video-cassette RL11437-VHS-0010)
  - 1988-1989 Season, 2
    - Hunting Cockroaches, 1988 (Box 1)
      Reviews, newspaper clippings
    - Soul Cookies and Traveling Ales, 1988 (Box 1)
      Newspaper clipping
    - Suddenly Last Summer, 1988; 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Night Songs, Street Songs, 1989; 2 folders (Box 1)
      Marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clippings, working script
    - Night Songs, Street Songs, 1989 (Box 16)
      Newspaper articles
    - Strange Snow, 1989; 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Strange Snow, 1989 (Box 5)
      Ticket reservation reports
  - 1989-1990 Season, 3
    - The Day Room, 1989; 2 folders (Box 1)
    - The Day Room, 1989 (Box 5)
    - The Day Room VHS, 1989 (Box 17, Video-cassette RL11437-VHS-0003)
    - The Day Room VHS, 1989 (Box 17, Video-cassette RL11437-VHS-0006)
    - Indecent Materials, 1989 (Box 16)
      Postcard
    - [Jesse?] Helms VHS, undated (Box 17, Video-cassette RL11437-VHS-0005)
    - The Illuminati, 1990; 2 folders (Box 1)
    - The Illuminati, 1990 (Box 5)
      Box office reports
    - Reports from the Holocaust and Indecent Materials, 1990; 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Reports from the Holocaust and Indecent Materials, 1990 (Box 5)
    - Kramer, 1990 (Box 5)
  - 1990-1991 Season, 4
    - The First Four Years: A Progress Report, 1991 (Box 16)
    - Indecent Materials, 1990 (Oversize-folder 1)
      Lobby Sign, Public Theater, New York
    - Grant proposal tape, Indecent Materials rehearsal, Larry Kramer Piece VHS, 1990 (Box 17, Video-cassette RL11437-VHS-0014)
    - The Dead Monkey, 1990 (Box 1)
    - The Dead Monkey, 1990 (Box 5)
      Box office reports, ticket reservation reports
    - Christmas on Mars, 1990-1991 (Box 1)
    - Christmas on Mars, 1990-1991 (Box 5)
    - The Love Suicide at Schofield Barracks, 1991 (Box 1)
    - The Love Suicide at Schofield Barracks Staged Reading, City Gallery, 1991 (Box 16)
      Program and postcard
    - The Love Suicide at Schofield Barracks, City Gallery VHS, 1991 (Box 17, Video-cassette RL11437-VHS-0019)
  - 1991-1992 Season, 5
    - Newsletter, brochure, Spring 1992 (Box 16)
    - Hotline, 1991; 3 folders (Box 1)
      Marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clippings, script
    - Hotline, 1991 (Box 5)
    - Hotline, 1991 (Box 16)
      Script
    - Hotline Opening VHS, 1991 (Box 17, Video-cassette RL11437-VHS-0007)
    - Hotline Opening Video VHS, 1991 (Box 17, Video-cassette RL11437-VHS-0023)
    - Hotline/TTY Call VHS, 1991 (Box 17, Video-cassette RL11437-VHS-0018)
    - Reckless, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Reckless, 1991 (Box 5)
    - Sincerity Forever, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Sincerity Forever, 1992 (Box 5)
    - The Key, 1992 (Box 1)
    - The Love Talker, 1992 (Box 1)
    - The Love Talker, 1992 (Box 5)
    - Fringe Movements, 1992 (Box 1)
      Contracts
    - Fringe Movements, 1992 (Box 5)
    - The Mystery of Irma Vep, 1992 (Box 1)
    - The Mystery of Irma Vep, 1992 (Box 5)
    - Scape, 1992 (Box 1)
    - The Red Address, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Jack, 1992 (Box 1)
    - In the Outfield, 1992 (Box 5)
  - 1992-1993 Season, 6
    - In the Outfield, 1992; 3 folders (Box 1)
      Marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clippings, contracts
    - In the Outfield, 1992 (Box 5)
    - Two Plays of Lanford Wilson: A Betrothal and A Poster of the Cosmos, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Two Plays of Lanford Wilson: A Betrothal and A Poster of the Cosmos, 1992 (Box 5)
    - A Poster of the Cosmos, David Ring VHS, 1992 (Box 17, Video-cassette RL11437-VHS-0022)
    - Night Songs, Street Songs, 1992; 3 folders (Box 1)
    - Night Songs, Street Songs, 1992; 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Night Songs, Street Songs, 1992 (Box 16)
      Music, programs, and script
    - Night Songs, Street Songs, 1992 (Box 16)
      Music
    - 7 Blowjobs, 1992; 4 folders (Box 1)
      Marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clippings, contracts, script
    - 7 Blowjobs, 1992 (Box 5)
    - Psycho Beach Party, 1993; 4 folders (Box 1)
      Marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clippings, contracts, box office reports
    - The Baltimore Waltz, 1993; 5 folders (Box 1)
      Marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clippings, contracts, box office reports, letter
    - Meat By Beat, 1993; 5 folders (Box 1)
      Marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clippings, contracts, box office reports, correspondence
    - One Day When I was Lost, 1993; 3 folders (Box 1)
      Marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clippings, box office reports
    - Outraged and on the Wire, 1993; 4 folders (Box 1)
    - Outraged and on the Wire, 1993 (Box 16)
    - Blue Window, 1993; 4 folders (Box 1)
    - Club Caffeine, 1993; 4 folders (Box 1)
      Marketing materials, contracts, box office reports, script
    - Club Caffeine, 1993 (Box 5)
    - Dark Ride, 1993; 3 folders (Box 1)
      Marketing materials, contracts, box office reports
    - Dark Ride Stock Footage VHS, 1993 (Box 17, Video-cassette RL11437-VHS-0016)
    - The Love Suicide at Schofield Barracks, 1993; 3 folders (Box 1)
    - Dark Ride, The General's Speech, Margo's TV's VHS, 1993 (Box 17, Video-cassette RL11437-VHS-0011)
  - 1993-1994 Season, 7
    - Progress Report, 1994 (Box 16)
    - If My Boundary Stops Here, 1993; 4 folders (Box 1)
    - The Love Suicide, 1993 (Box 16)
    - The Mystery of Irma Vep, 1993; 4 folders (Box 1)
    - The Mystery of Irma Vep VHS, 1993 (Box 17, Video-cassette RL11437-VHS-0002)
    - Down the Road, 1993-1994; 4 folders (Box 1)
    - The High Risk Group Southern Garage Dancers, 1994; 3 folders (Box 2)
    - Love and Anger, 1994; 2 folders (Box 2)
      Marketing materials, box office reports
    - Bound and Gagged, 1994; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Abe on a Hot Tin Roof, 1994; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Mama's Children, 1994; 2 folders (Box 2)
      Contracts, box office reports
    - Cassandra's Lullaby, 1994; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Don't Ask Don't Tell, 1994 (Box 2)
    - You're Just Like My Father, 1994; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - In the Outfield, 1994 (Box 2)
    - Reynolds Price Reading, 1994 (Box 2)
      Reviews, newspaper clippings, box office reports
    - Let the Crooked Flower Speak, 1994 (Box 2)
    - Fort Head, 1994 (Box 2)
    - Straight Talk, 1994; 2 folders (Box 2)
      Reviews, newspaper clippings, box office reports, script
    - Dark Fruit, 1994 (Box 2)
    - Why We Never Danced, 1994 (Box 2)
    - My Queer Body, 1994; 4 folders (Box 2)
      Marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clippings, box office reports, letters of support
    - Execution of Justice, 1994; 3 folders (Box 2)
    - Execution of Justice, 1994 (Box 16)
      Slides
    - Always Sometimes Never, 1994; 4 folders (Box 2)
  - 1994-1995 Season, 8
    - Placebo VHS, 1994 (Box 17, Video-cassette RL11437-VHS-0021)
    - Night Songs, Street Songs, 1994 (Box 16)
      Jeff and Ed correspondence, music sheets
    - Sound and Beauty, 1994; 3 folders (Box 2)
    - Brilliant Traces, 1994 (Box 2)
    - Buena Vista, 1994 (Box 2)
    - The Swan, 1994; 4 folders (Box 2)
    - Lonely Planet, 1995; 4 folders (Box 2)
    - Brute Theater, 1995; 4 folders (Box 2)
    - Landscape Silence & Night, 1995; 4 folders (Box 2)
    - Oscar Over Here, 1995; 4 folders (Box 2)
    - Reading Series, 1995 (Box 2)
    - Clit Notes, 1995; 3 folders (Box 2)
    - H.I.Vato, 1995; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Fishing for Virginia, 1995; 3 folders (Box 2)
    - Randy's House, 1995 (Box 2)
    - Ten-In-One, 1995; 4 folders (Box 2)
    - Imagine Being More Afraid, 1995; 3 folders (Box 2)
    - Taken by the Faeries, 1995; 4 folders (Box 2)
  - 1995-1996-Season, 9
    - Newspaper article, 1995 (Box 16)
      News and Observer newspaper article on Jeff
    - Vampire Lesbians/Sleeping Beauty, 1995-1996; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Vampire Lesbians/Sleeping Beauty, 1995 (Box 4)
      Marketing materials, correspondence, box office reports, budgets
    - Tone Clusters, 1996; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Tone Clusters, 1996; 2 folders (Box 4)
      Marketing materials, contracts, budgets
    - Friendly Fire, 1996; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - The Cryptogram, 1996; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - The Cryptogram, 1996 (Box 4)
      Form letters, box office reports
    - The Cryptogram, 1996 (Box 16)
      Promotional material
    - The Bible Belt, 1996; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - The Bible Belt, 1996 (Box 4)
  - 1996-1997 Season, 10
    - Slavs!, 1996; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Slavs!, 1996 (Box 4)
      Marketing materials, box office reports, rehearsal reports, schedule
    - Somewhere in the Pacific, 1996; 4 folders (Box 2)
      Marketing materials, contracts, box office reports, correspondence
    - Slaughter City, 1996; 3 folders (Box 2)
    - The Condemned, 1997; 3 folders (Box 2)
    - The Moonshot Tape/Poaster of the Cosmos, 1997; 3 folders (Box 2)
    - Walking Miracles, 1997; 4 folders (Box 2)
      Marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clippings, box office reports, expense reports
    - Walking Miracles, 1997 (Box 16)
      Binder
    - Love in the Time of College, 1997; 5 folders (Box 2)
  - 1997-1998 Season, 11
    - Buena Vista, 1997; 4 folders (Box 3)
    - Walking Miracles, 1997; 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Posing Naked, 1998 (Box 3)
    - Eulogy for a Warrior, 1998; 5 folders (Box 3)
      Marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clippings, contracts, box office reports, expense reports
    - The Food Chain, 1998; 3 folders (Box 3)
      Marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clippings, box office reports, correspondence, rehearsal schedule
  - 1998-1999 Season, 12
    - How I Learned to Drive, 1998; 4 folders (Box 3)
      Marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clippings, box office reports, correspondence
    - How I Learned to Drive, 1998 (Box 16)
    - Winding the Ball, 1998; 3 folders (Box 3)
    - The Night Larry Kramer Kissed Me, 1998; 3 folders (Box 3)
    - Blue Roses, 1998; 3 folders (Box 3)
    - TRU, 1998; 3 folders (Box 3)
    - Contents Under Pressure/Courage Under Fire, 1999; 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Somewhere in the Pacific, 1999; 3 folders (Box 3)
      Marketing materials, box office reports, staging information
    - Preaching to the Perverted, 1999; 4 folders (Box 3)
    - Crimson & Clover, 1999; 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Amor Fortuna, 1999; 5 folders (Box 3)
      Marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clippings, contracts, box office reports, receipts
    - Cloud Tectonics, 1999; 3 folders (Box 3)
      Marketing materials, box office reports, correspondence, photographs
    - Cloud Tectonics, 1999 (Box 16)
      Program
    - Shirts & Skin, 1999; 4 folders (Box 3)
  - 1999-2000 Season, 13
    - Stop Kiss, 1999 (Box 3)
    - King Lear, 1999; 3 folders (Box 3)
    - The Mystery of Irma Vep, 1999; 4 folders (Box 3)
      Marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clippings, box office reports, script
    - Walking Miracles VHS, 1999 (Box 17, Video-cassette RL11437-VHS-0015)
    - What Was Lost, 2000 (Box 4)
    - Private Eyes, 2000; 2 folders (Box 4)
    - One Noble Journey, 2000; 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Ein Kleiner Kowboy (sic), 2000; 3 folders (Box 4)
    - Emma's Child, 2000; 3 folders (Box 4)
    - A Mouthfulla Sacco & Vanzetti (sic), 2000; 4 folders (Box 4)
      Marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clippings, box office reports, script, photograph
    - Glory Box, 2000; 3 folders (Box 4)
    - Step Out, 2000; 2 folders (Box 4)
      Marketing materials, reviews, box office reports
    - 802701 (sic), 2000; 3 folders (Box 4)
      Marketng materials, box office reports, script
  - 2000-2001 Season, 14
    - Theater reviews, 2000 (Box 16)
    - And Baby Makes Seven, 2000; 3 folders (Box 4)
    - Last Train to Nibroc, 2000; 5 folders (Box 4)
    - One Noble Journey, 2000; 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Alien Planet, 2000; 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Fuddy Meers, 2000-2001; 4 folders (Box 4)
      Marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clippings, box office reports, correspondence, photographs
    - Fuddy Meers, 2000-2001 (Box 16)
    - Preaching to the Perverted (Holly Hughes), 2001; 5 folders (Box 4)
      Marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clippings, box office reports, correspondence, script
    - Preaching to the Perverted audiocassette, 2001 (Box 7, Audio-cassette RL11437-CS-0001)
      "Tommy - keep on the sunny side"
    - The Monogamist, 2001; 4 folders (Box 4)
      Marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clippings, box office reports, expense reports, photographs
    - Tune for Tommy, 2001; 3 folders (Box 4)
      Marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clippings, box office reports, photographs
    - Tune for Tommy, 2001 (Box 16)
    - A New Fine Shame, 2001; 3 folders (Box 4)
    - Puzzlehunt 2001, 5 folders (Box 4)
      Marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clippings, contracts, connect-the-dots puzzle
    - PuzzleHunt 2001 (Box 16)
      Brochure
    - Puzzle Hunt 2001 window dub VHS (Box 17, Video-cassette RL11437-VHS-0017)
  - 2001-2002 Season, 15
    - Theater reviews, 2001 (Box 16)
    - This is Our Youth, 2001; 2 folders (Box 4)
      Marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clippings, box office reports, photograph
    - This is Our Youth pre-show CD, 2001 (Box 7, Audio-cd RL11437-CD-0001)
    - Something Wonderful Right Now: An Evening of Improvisational Theater, 2001; 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Cymbeline, 2001; 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Breathtaking, 2001; 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Fit to be Tied, 2001-2002; 3 folders (Box 5)
      Marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clippings, box office reports, performance rights
    - Surviving Pearl: A Baroque Love Story, 2001; 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Prufrock, 2002; 2 folders (Box 5)
      Marketing materials, contract, box office reports
    - A Tune for Tommy, 2002; 3 folders (Box 5)
    - Plays Well with Others, 2002; 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Hurricane Salad, 2002; 2 folders (Box 5)
      Marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clippings, contract, box office reports
    - Puzzlehunt 2002, 4 folders (Box 5)
      Marketing materials, newspaper clippings, photographs
    - Don't Ask Don't Tell, 2002; 2 folders (Box 5)
      Marketing materials, newspaper clipping, box office reports, photographs
    - Don't Ask Don't Tell CD-R, 2002 (Box 7, Optical-disc RL11437-OP-0001)
      "Manbites Dog Theater postcard PDFs, Kelly Martin Willow Graphics"
    - Peep, 2002; 2 folders (Box 5)
    - 70 Scenes of Halloween, 2002 (Box 16)
      Scripts
  - 2002-2003 Season, 16
    - Season program, 2002 (Box 16)
    - Tomorrowland, 2002 (Box 16)
    - Bucknaked, 2003; 3 folders (Box 5)
      Marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clippings, contract papers, box office reports
    - Bucknaked, 2003 (Box 16)
      Collection
    - Silver Screen Peep, 2003 (Box 5)
    - Loose Lips Sink Ships, 2003 (Box 5)
    - Scott Miller, 2003 (Box 5)
      Marketing materials, newspaper clippings, box office reports
    - Manbites Dog Music, Scott Miller, 2003 (Box 7, Audio-cd RL11437-CD-0002)
      "Help us bring live music to the Manbites Dog stage"
    - Manbites Dog Music, Scott Miller, 2003 (Box 17, Audio-cd RL11437-CD-0015)
    - Puzzlehunt 2003 (Box 5)
    - Puzzlehunt Window dub VHS, 2003 (Box 17, Video-cassette RL11437-VHS-0008)
    - Kenny Roby (with Scott McCall) & Richard Ferreira, 2003 (Box 5)
    - Mouth Candy presents Open Wide, 2003 (Box 6)
      Marketing materials, box office report
    - Two Sams, 2003 (Box 6)
      Marketing materials, box office reports, rehearsal schedule
  - 2003-2004 Season, 17
    - Bill & Libby Hicks, 2003 (Box 6)
      Marketing materials, box office reports, photographs
    - Minstrel Show, 2003 (Box 6)
    - Us, 2003 (Box 6)
    - Take it all Off, 2003 (Box 6)
    - Kevin Gordon, 2003 (Box 6)
    - Mouth Candy presents Say Ahh!, 2003 (Box 6)
    - Shirlette Ammons Live, 2003 (Box 6)
    - Julius Caesar, 2003 (Box 6)
      Marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clippings, box office reports,
    - Gothic, 2003 (Box 6)
      Marketing materials, newspaper clipping, box office reports
    - Tiny Ninja Theater's Romeo and Juliet, 2003 (Box 6)
    - Shopping and Fucking, 2003; 2 folders (Box 6)
      Marketing materials, box office reports, script, photographs
    - Frog Holler, 2003 (Box 6)
    - Transactors Improv Co., 2004 (Box 6)
    - 501: Evolution of a Butch Lesbian, 2004 (Box 6)
    - Evening of Blues / Folk, 2004 (Box 6)
      Box office report
    - Silver River, 2004; 3 folders (Box 6)
      Marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clippings, contracts, box office reports, photographs
    - Silver River CD-R, 2004 (Box 7, Optical-disc RL11437-OP-0002)
      "Silver River"
    - Holding Talks, 2004 (Box 6)
      Marketing materials, newspaper clipping, contracts, box office reports
    - Smut, 2004 (Box 6)
    - Far Away, 2004 (Box 6)
    - Brooms, 2004 (Box 6)
    - Mouth Candy presents Lip Service, 2004 (Box 6)
    - Nixon's Nixon, 2004 (Box 6)
  - 2004-2005 Season, 18
    - Sonnets for an Old Century, 2004 (Box 6)
      Marketing materials, reviews, newspaper clipping, box office reports, script
    - Sonnets for an Old Century Final for show, Sound Q's show use CD-R, undated (Box 17, Cd RL11437-CD-0014)
    - The Tempest, 2004 (Box 6)
    - 501: Evolution of a Butch Lesbian, 2004 (Box 6)
    - Vincent: An Appreciation of Edna St. Vincent Millay, 2004 (Box 6)
      Marketing materials, reviews, box office reports, script, photograph
    - Vincent: An Appreciation of Edna St. Vincent Millay sound, 2004 (Box 7, Audio-cd RL11437-CD-0006)
      "Pre-show/intro and post-curtain"
    - Vincent: An Appreciation of Edna St. Vincent Millay sound, 2004 (Box 7, Audio-cd RL11437-CD-0007)
      "Blind Boys of Alabama / Spirit of the Century"
    - Vincent: An Appreciation of Edna St. Vincent Millay sound, 2004 (Box 7, Audio-cd RL11437-CD-0008)
      "Maldoror Sound"
    - Tiny Ninja Theater presents Macbeth, 2004 (Box 6)
    - Nixon's Nixon, 2005 (Box 6)
    - Nixon's Nixon sounds, 2005 (Box 7, Audio-cd RL11437-CD-0003)
      "Nixon Sounds," 2005 January 3
    - Nixon's Nixon sounds, 2005 (Box 7, Audio-cd RL11437-CD-0004)
      "Nixon 2 - Sound," 2005 January 5
    - Nixon's Nixon sounds, 2005 (Box 7, Audio-cd RL11437-CD-0005)
      "Nixon - added sounds, test disc"
    - Nixon's Nixon sounds, 2004 (Box 7, Audio-cd RL11437-CD-0009)
      "Nixon's Nixon sound," 2004 August 10
    - Nixon's Nixon sounds, 2004 (Box 7, Audio-cd RL11437-CD-0010)
      "Nixon sound," 2004 August 9
    - The Man Who, 2005 (Box 6)
    - Right now this minute: a script in development, 2005 (Box 6)
      both hands theare company (sic); marketing materials, box office reports
    - Silver River, 2005 (Box 6)
      Stoneleaf Festival of North Carolina Theatre; marketing materials, contracts, correspondence
    - Dragon Lady, 2005 (Box 6)
    - Puzzlehunt 2005, 3 folders (Box 6)
      Marketing materials, newspaper clippings, script, surveys
    - Puzzlehunt 2005 CD (Box 7, Optical-disc RL11437-OP-0003)
      "Puzzlehunt 2005"
    - Puzzlehunt 2005 VHS (Box 17, Video-cassette RL11437-VHS-0001)
    - Songs & Scenes from Sam/Sara, 2005 (Box 6)
      Marketing materials, box office reports, script
  - 2005-2006 Season, 19
    - Independent newspaper review, 2005 (Box 16)
    - Found Magazine/Lone Surfer Tour, 2005 (Box 6)
      Marketing materials, box office report, correspondence